<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">KotlinDemo</string>

    <string name="negotiable">面议</string>
    <string name="recommend_similar_jobs">为你推荐相似好职位</string>
    <string name="next">下一个</string>
    <string name="please_select_job">请选择职位</string>
    <string name="delivery_job">投递%s个职位dd</string>
    <string name="title_content">[] Mark: ThePeople测试成都市哈哈哈这是不适合觉得亟待解决的卡卡卡壳不是对你的狄安娜看卡卡吧卡卡卡看看卡卡卡卡卡会不会复活后哈哈哈哈哈哈不是合适哦了是v年历史</string>
    <string name="title_content_expand">Please Mark: The people people people people The people people people people.</string>
    <string name="title_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="title_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="title_unmarked">6 unmarked</string>
    <string name="title_test">Includes APIs for testing your Android app, including Espresso, JUnit Runner, JUnit4 rules, and UI Automator.have less code, powerful tools, and intuitive Kotlin APIs.</string>
    <string name="title_test2">安卓提供各种尖端工具和功能可帮助您针对数十亿用户日常使用的手机平板电脑电视和汽车来构建应用</string>
    <string name="long_text_en" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">\t\t\t\tAs you know, this website is not only about living a long, healthy life but also about doing something with it. And this new research is great news if you\'re looking to make a difference. Creating and contributing to the world is not only a foundational piece of living a healthy and happy life, but also a meaningful one.\n \t\t\t\tYou can\'t control the amount of time you spend on this planet, but you can control what you contribute while you\'re here. These contributions don\'t have to be major endeavors. Cook a meal instead of buying one. Play a game instead of watching one. Write a paragraph instead of reading one. You don\'t have to create big contributions, you just need to live out small ones each day.\n \t\t\t\tToo often we spend our lives visiting the world instead of shaping it. Be an adventurer, an inventor, an entrepreneur, an artist. Suggest your own ideas instead of reacting to everyone else\'s. Be an active participant in life and contribute to the world around you. Make good conversation. Make good art. Make good adventure. But above all, make something. Contributing and creating doesn\'t just make you feel alive, it keeps you alive.As you know, this website is not only about living a long, healthy life but also about doing something with it. And this new research is great news if you\'re looking to make a difference. Creating and contributing to the world is not only a foundational piece of living a healthy and happy life, but also a meaningful one.\n \t\t\t\tYou can\'t control the amount of time you spend on this planet, but you can control what you contribute while you\'re here. These contributions don\'t have to be major endeavors. Cook a meal instead of buying one. Play a game instead of watching one. Write a paragraph instead of reading one. You don\'t have to create big contributions, you just need to live out small ones each day.\n \t\t\t\tToo often we spend our lives visiting the world instead of shaping it. Be an adventurer, an inventor, an entrepreneur, an artist. Suggest your own ideas instead of reacting to everyone else\'s.
    </string>
</resources>
